<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Triad Real Estate Podcast with Jason Bramblett</title>
    <link>localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Jason Bramblett and Associates - your professional Triad Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Jason Bramblett</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2018-06-12 14:58:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Jason Bramblett</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Jason@JasonBramblett.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Jason Bramblett</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Triad Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Jason Bramblett and Associates - your professional Triad Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hire Us for the Best Experience Selling Your Home</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/hire-us-for-best-experience-selling.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2018-06-06 14:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/Hire+Us+To+Get+The+Best+Service+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

A question I get on occasion is, “How do I know I am getting the best person to sell my home?”


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


Well, I think that our company is a great solution to your real estate needs. It has been around for 20 years and we have developed systems and proven strategies that work right here in the Triad community.

I’ve focused on is developing and hiring the best people. We have a phenomenal training program. I look for the best people in the business, bring them on, and plug them into our proven trackable system. We can then see the win-win results.

It doesn’t really matter to us if you are selling to reach the top of the market or selling as-is, we have a plan in the service for everybody.

You can talk to friends, or perhaps you have seen our advertising on TV or billboards, to learn more about our reputation. Our online reviews show how many homes we’ve sold.

The biggest thing we like to have you do is see our operation and how we work in person. This is something you should do with everybody. A lot of real estate agents work out of their homes part-time and are unorganized. Seeing the flow and the production says a lot about the success of the company.

“IT DOESN’T REALLY MATTER TO US IF YOU ARE SELLING TO REACH THE TOP OF THE MARKET OR SELLING AS-IS, WE HAVE A PLAN IN THE SERVICE FOR EVERYBODY.”

You will see that we will be successful at selling your home. We sell a lot of homes that have been on the market many times with many different companies. One of the things that we hear when people come here is that they sense a sense of urgency. They can see and experience the professionalism by coming to our office.

If you would like to come check us out to see if we would be a good fit for you, call or email me. I look forward to speaking with you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/Hire+Us+To+Get+The+Best+Service+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/Hire+Us+To+Get+The+Best+Service+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

A question I get on occasion is, “How do I know I am getting the best person to sell my home?”

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

A question I get on occasion is, “How do I know I am getting the best person to sell my home?”

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Whats Behind Declining Home Prices?</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/whats-behind-declining-home-prices.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2018-05-02 10:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/Why+Are+Home+Prices+Dropping%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Homeowners in the Triad are frustrated. Inventory is low, demand for their homes is high, and they’re receiving multiple offers from prospective buyers, but home prices are still dropping.


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


How can that be? Supply and demand economics would say that if there’s only a little bit of something that a lot of people want, the price should go up.

In real estate, things don’t always work this way. The factor that is causing this counterintuitive price drop is the banks. Banks don’t care that you’re pushing home values up; they feel that a given home is worth X amount, therefore, the amount they will loan will reflect that.

Now, the buyer can pay the difference out of pocket, but we’re seeing in certain price ranges that that is not always the case.

“BE CAUTIOUS OUT THERE IF YOU’RE A HOMEOWNER.”

Be cautious out there if you’re a homeowner attempting to sell your home. Just because you get the highest and best offer doesn’t necessarily mean that it’s going to stick. It could come right back down to where it might have been in a more reasonable market.

If you need help, I’m here for you. We’ve been doing this a long time, so we can walk you through the process, make sure that we diligently price your property to get top dollar, and get every offer to stay. Do you really want to see a house four or five times just to get an offer to stick? We’ll always get you the most money in the shortest amount of time.

For any questions or if you need assistance, feel free to reach out to me. I’d be glad to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/Why+Are+Home+Prices+Dropping%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/Why+Are+Home+Prices+Dropping%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Homeowners in the Triad are frustrated. Inventory is low, demand for their homes is high, and they’re receiving multiple offers from prospective buyers, but home prices are still dropping.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Homeowners in the Triad are frustrated. Inventory is low, demand for their homes is high, and they’re receiving multiple offers from prospective buyers, but home prices are still dropping.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Your Spring 2018 Market Update</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/your-spring-2018-market-update.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2018-03-30 10:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/How+Is+The+Spring+Market%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

It’s officially spring, so what can we expect from the spring real estate market?


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


It’s exciting to see that prices are actually increasing and that homes are starting to appreciate in the marketplace, which we haven’t seen in 10 years, at least.

Nationally, inventory is very low, and it’s likely we’ll run out. How do we overcome that?

“IT’S A GREAT TIME TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF LOW INVENTORY.”

As buyers reach out to us about certain areas, cities, and neighborhoods, we’ll reach out to homeowners to introduce them to buyers. If they’re a good fit, maybe you’ll consider selling your home. It’s a great time to take advantage of low inventory if you’re a homeowner who is mobile.

If you’d like to upsize or downsize your housing situation or just look at the value of your home in the Triad area, feel free to reach out to us.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/How+Is+The+Spring+Market%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/How+Is+The+Spring+Market%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

It’s officially spring, so what can we expect from the spring real estate market?

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

It’s officially spring, so what can we expect from the spring real estate market?

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Use a Local Lender?</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/why-use-local-lender.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2018-03-01 13:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/Why+You+Should+Use+A+Local+Lender+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

One of the things I get questioned about a lot is mortgage lending. Many people tell me, “I used this bank last time I refinanced my house and that went pretty good so I think I’ll use them again.” However, be careful. These large lenders offer what may appear to be a discount, but they make it up in additional junk fees.


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


Here’s what we are finding. People are being enticed by working with these big online lenders, but these lenders aren’t giving the right information, funds, or materials in order to close on time. With our local lenders, we see the opposite. When you work with a local lender, you are much more likely to close on time.

“WORKING WITH A LOCAL LENDER MAKES A HUGE, HUGE DIFFERENCE.”

We recently had a person who thought they had everything taken care of with their online lender, but the loan didn’t close when it was supposed to. They are now going to have to stay in a hotel all weekend with their moving truck because we couldn’t get the loan closed.

If moving in on a specific day is important, don’t risk it by saving $4 a month on your payment. Working with a local lender makes a huge, huge difference. We have two great local lenders we’d be happy to connect you with.

If you have any other questions or need anything else, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/Why+You+Should+Use+A+Local+Lender+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2018/Why+You+Should+Use+A+Local+Lender+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

One of the things I get questioned about a lot is mortgage lending. Many people tell me, “I used this bank last time I refinanced my house and that went pretty good so I think I’ll use them again.” However, be careful. These large lenders offer what may appear to be a discount, but they make it up in additional junk fees.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

One of the things I get questioned about a lot is mortgage lending. Many people tell me, “I used this bank last time I refinanced my house and that went pretty good so I think I’ll use them again.” However, be careful. These large lenders offer what may appear to be a discount, but they make it up in additional junk fees.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Wed Love to Help You in 2018</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/wed-love-to-help-you-in-2018.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate Other</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2018-01-08 10:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

I hope everybody had a phenomenal year in 2017. I hope you achieved your goals and are ready to make some new ones.


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


We saw more home appreciation in the Triad Area in 2017 than we had in the previous 10 years! I think that trend is going to continue right along in 2018. This is going to be the best year to sell your home in the last decade from what I can tell.

If you didn’t get your home sold this year, give us a call and we will make sure that it does. We were able to serve over 580 families in 2017 and we hope to serve another 1,000 in 2018. We’d love to add you and your family to our list of fantastic clients.

“WE’D LOVE TO ADD YOU TO OUR LIST OF CLIENTS.”

If you have any questions for us about real estate or there is anything that you need help with, don’t hesitate to give us a call or send us an email. We would love to hear from you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

I hope everybody had a phenomenal year in 2017. I hope you achieved your goals and are ready to make some new ones.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

I hope everybody had a phenomenal year in 2017. I hope you achieved your goals and are ready to make some new ones.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why You Should Consider Selling This Winter</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/why-you-should-consider-selling-this.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2017-12-08 11:34:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Selling+During+The+Holdaiys+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Inventory is low and demand is high. It’s the perfect storm for home sellers.


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


One question that we get asked frequently during this time of year is, “Should we sell in the winter?” This year, the answer is yes. Absolutely. This is a golden year for you to get top dollar for your home.

“THE SITUATION IS LIKE THIS ACROSS THE TRIAD.”

Inventory levels across the country are down and there are hundreds of buyers on our site looking for homes just like yours. Some are getting frustrated and deciding to build new homes because they can’t find anything. There are a ton of people relocating to the area right now who are looking for properties as well. The situation is like this across the Triad.

Buyers are serious right now and are searching with a mission. If you or someone you know has been entertaining the idea of selling a home, get in touch with us. We’d be happy to help you take advantage of this seller’s market.

In the meantime, we hope you had a great Thanksgiving and have an even better Christmas. Happy holidays!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Selling+During+The+Holdaiys+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Selling+During+The+Holdaiys+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Inventory is low and demand is high. It’s the perfect storm for home sellers.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Inventory is low and demand is high. It’s the perfect storm for home sellers.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Our Home Selling Guarantee</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/our-home-selling-guarantee.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2017-08-30 16:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Our+Home+Selling+Guarantee+-+Jason+Bramblett+Real+Estate.mp4</guid>
        <description>

At Jason Bramblett Real Estate, we have only one goal: to get your home sold.


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


At Jason Bramblett Real Estate, we have only one goal: to sell your home quickly and for top dollar.

There’s a big difference between getting a listing and selling your home. Most real estate agents work with both buyers and sellers. We believe this creates a conflict of interest for you, the seller. This means that even if a buyer doesn’t buy your home, the agent could still sell them any home on the market and make commission off that sale.

Our listing agents at Jason Bramblett Real Estate are not allowed to work with buyers—as a result, they can devote 100% of their time to getting your home sold. If we don’t sell, we don’t get paid.

“IF WE DON’T SELL, WE DON’T GET PAID.”

With our Coming Soon marketing program, we change your position from reactive to proactive, getting you the most money for your home. We’ll make sure to root out all the deal-killing snags that may come up and offer third-party services to you at a hugely discounted price.

Don’t believe us? See what Barbara Corcoran has to say in the video above.

To learn more about our marketing strategy or talk to an agent about selling your home, give us a call. We look forward to working with you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Our+Home+Selling+Guarantee+-+Jason+Bramblett+Real+Estate.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Our+Home+Selling+Guarantee+-+Jason+Bramblett+Real+Estate.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

At Jason Bramblett Real Estate, we have only one goal: to get your home sold.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

At Jason Bramblett Real Estate, we have only one goal: to get your home sold.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Handle a Multiple-Offer Situation?</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/how-can-you-handle-multiple-offer.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2017-08-16 14:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/How+Can+You+Handle+a+Multiple-Offer+Situation%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I wanted to take some time to talk to you about how to handle multiple-offer situations as both a buyer and a seller.


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


We’ve gotten this question a couple of times in the last few months, and today I wanted to take the time to talk about how to handle multiple-offer situations.

From a seller’s standpoint, having multiple offers is typically a good thing. You do have to be careful though. I have seen situations where a home has multiple offers, and then the seller gets a little too aggressive and ends up with no offers because everyone withdraws for whatever reason.

We can coach you on how to handle multiple offers as a seller. The power of a third-party negotiator such as a real estate agent typically always yields a higher price for the home.

From a buyer’s perspective, it can be a little bit scary to find yourself in a multiple-offer situation. Making your offer as clean as possible and allowing some of the terms to appease the seller is going to make it stand out amongst the competition.

“WE CAN COACH YOU ON HOW TO HANDLE MULTIPLE OFFERS AS A SELLER.”

Now I didn’t say to make your offer have the highest price. There are aspects of an offer outside of the price that the seller will look at. Adjusting your offer to meet the seller’s needs, such as a specific closing time and date, will sometimes put your offer to the top of the list.

If you need some help with multiple-offer situations, both our buyer and our listing teams have been coached through many similar situations and can help you navigate that process easily.

If you have any other questions about this topic or you’re looking to buy or sell a home, please give me a call. I’d be happy to help!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/How+Can+You+Handle+a+Multiple-Offer+Situation%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/How+Can+You+Handle+a+Multiple-Offer+Situation%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today I wanted to take some time to talk to you about how to handle multiple-offer situations as both a buyer and a seller.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today I wanted to take some time to talk to you about how to handle multiple-offer situations as both a buyer and a seller.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Do You Need Representation as a Buyer During New Home Construction ?</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/do-you-need-representation-as-buyer.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate Buyers Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2017-08-01 17:39:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

It’s very important to have representation as a buyer. Here are a few reasons why.


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


Do you need an agent representing you when buying a new home?

In our opinion, it’s very important to have representation as a buyer. When you visit a model home or a sales office, the person there isn’t working for you. They are working for the builder and have their best interests in mind. It behooves you to have someone acting in your best interest as well. They are a second set of eyes on the paperwork and on all of the details in the contract. There are certain fees and non-refundable deposits that they are aware of. You might miss those if you’re doing things on your own.

“HIRING AGENT REPRESENTATION IS ESSENTIAL.”

As someone who has been in real estate for a long time, I know the process of how to walk you through new construction from start to finish. I know the things to look for and can put leverage on the builder if things start to run behind. A huge benefit of hiring a buyer’s agent is their ability to juggle things around so that you have a smooth closing. They can also help be an advocate for other resources you may need such as an attorney, a home inspector, or a mortgage lender.

Having agent representation during the new construction process is essential, whether you’re building your first home or your 12th. The extra professional looking out for your best interests is always a welcome addition.

If you have any questions about hiring a buyer’s agent or anything else relating to the buying process, give me a call or send me an email. I would love to help you out.
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

It’s very important to have representation as a buyer. Here are a few reasons why.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

It’s very important to have representation as a buyer. Here are a few reasons why.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Should You Consider Buying an Older Triad Home?</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/should-you-consider-buying-older-triad.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate Buyers Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2017-06-22 11:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Should+You+Consider+Buying+an+Older+Triad+Home%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Thinking of buying an older home? You need to think about whether the charm and character of the home outweigh the potential maintenance risks.


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


Are you thinking about buying an older house? If so, how do you know if it’s a wise investment?

Older homes typically need a little more maintenance and love, but that shouldn’t stop you from considering older homes if you have a solid budget. However, I think there are a few select groups that are probably better off not buying an older home:

• People just starting out their first home search
  • Those without three to six months’ worth of emergency funds
  • Anyone living paycheck to paycheck (You might even want a new home with a warranty)

Just be cautious when shopping for homes; I see many homebuyers get into trouble buying an older home because of the location and taking on the risk of an older home. For example, if a house is 10 years old, it will probably need a new roof in the next 10 years. Some newer homes come with 30-year architectural shingles that you don’t have to worry about for a very long time.

“OLDER HOMES COME WITH MORE POTENTIAL MAINTENANCE RISKS THAN NEWER HOMES.”

If you’re considering an older home, just make sure you’re not only OK with these potential maintenance costs and headaches, but prepared for them as well. Have an emergency fund and be ready for things to need replacing.

If you have any other questions about buying a home or selling a home here in the Triad, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email soon. I’d be glad to help.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Should+You+Consider+Buying+an+Older+Triad+Home%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Should+You+Consider+Buying+an+Older+Triad+Home%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Thinking of buying an older home? You need to think about whether the charm and character of the home outweigh the potential maintenance risks.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Thinking of buying an older home? You need to think about whether the charm and character of the home outweigh the potential maintenance risks.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Is It Wise to Buy a Home Near a Large Power Line?</title>
        <link>localhost:4000/is-it-wise-to-buy-home-near-large-power.html</link>
        
          <category>Triad Real Estate Buyers Tips</category>
        
        <author>Jason Bramblett</author>
        <pubDate>2017-06-05 10:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Is+It+Wise+to+Buy+a+Home+Near+a+Large+Power+Line%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Homes located near large power lines can present a great opportunity if they have the right price and you’re buying one for the right reasons.


Selling your Triad area home? Get a free home analysis report
Buying a Triad area home? Search all homes for sale


Should you buy a home near power lines and will that ever harm your family?

As to whether it’s safe or not, I’ll let you determine that for yourself. In my 19 years in real estate, I’ve found that homes located near large power lines present an added risk to the buyer, and sellers tend to struggle selling them in our market. These properties have one of the highest foreclosure rates.

However, they can also be a good investment opportunity as rentals. I’ve seen some of them be discounted by as much as 30% to 40%, and these homes were located in great neighborhoods as well. As far as renters are concerned, they know that they’ll only be there a short time, and the quality of the home is typically fantastic.

“HOMES NEAR POWER LINES CAN BE GREAT AS RENTAL PROPERTIES.”

The prospect of buying one for your family is a decision you’ll have to make, but I’ve seen phenomenal opportunities to buy discounted real estate in neighborhoods near large power lines. There is only a small percentage of people who won’t buy a home near a large power line, just like there is only a small percentage of people who won’t buy a home near a pond, a busy street, or a corner lot.

Would I shy away from one of these homes? Not for the right price and the right reasons to buy.

If you have any questions about this topic or you’re looking to buy or sell a home in our market, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I look forward to helping you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Is+It+Wise+to+Buy+a+Home+Near+a+Large+Power+Line%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Jason+Bramblett/Videos/2017/Is+It+Wise+to+Buy+a+Home+Near+a+Large+Power+Line%253F+-+Triad+Real+Estate+Agent.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Homes located near large power lines can present a great opportunity if they have the right price and you’re buying one for the right reasons.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Jason Bramblett</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Homes located near large power lines can present a great opportunity if they have the right price and you’re buying one for the right reasons.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Triad, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Jason Bramblett</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Jason Bramblett</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Jason Bramblett and Associates - your professional Triad Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
